http://genamics.com/privacypolicy.htm

Genamics Privacy Policy
Genamics has drafted this document, which details how we gather and disseminate information, in an effort to demonstrate our strong commitment to online privacy. Please contact us if you have any questions about our privacy policy.
Use of Internet Protocol Address
We use your Internet protocol (IP) address for several reasons: to help diagnose problems with our server, to administer our Web site, and to gather broad demographic information.
Use of Order Information
When you place an order, Genamics requests information such as contact information, credit card number and demographic information. The contact information you provide is used to send your orders only. No promotional material will be sent. Your financial information is used for the sole purpose of billing you for products and services.
Security
Genamics features a secure server to protect the loss, misuse or alteration of information placed under our control.
Children's Guidelines
We do not collect or use any online contact information or identifiable off-line contact information about a child without parental consent. We do not distribute personally identifiable information about children without parental consent. We do not give children the ability to post or distribute personal information without prior consent. We do not entice children with games or contests that would encourage them to disclose personal information.
Opt Out/Opt In
Genamics allows users to opt out of receiving e-mail from us or our partners. To opt out of our mailing list you can send e-mail to a remove mailing list.
Correct/Update Personal Information
Genamics allows you to change or modify your personal information by sending e-mail to a remove e-mail address or by visiting a designated customer service page.
Disclaimer
This site contains links to other sites. Genamics is not responsible for the content or privacy practices of these sites.
